One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Rubber
Bazooka!
Alright.
You okay?
Sorry for the trouble, Straw Hat.
Thank you, Luffy-chin!
It's fine!
You're done over there too, huh?
Yes
You people truly are amazing.
No matter how many of'em show up, I wouldn't lose to someone like that!
Damn...! He's too strong...!
300 million is impossible after all.
Right now, there are more big shots on the archipelago than ever before, too...
Damn! If we could just get one of them...
But, what was that?
The Embers of History
So many bounty-hunters suddenly showed up...
That was the third group to attack us.
I can't even see that food-sampling, uhh...
...I mean, souvenir-shop any more...
There are fewer people around, and the shops and cities, feel rather suspicious.
It doesn't seem like the kind of place where we would find a coating mechanic.
This archipelago is huge, so there are places where the government's eyes can't reach.
The marines won't go anywhere near this place.
Have a look at this.
A map, is it?
It classifies the groves in groups of ten, based on their specific traits.
Nothing is set in stone,
Grove 1~29 Lawless Zone Amusement Park Hotels Tourist Zone Marine HQ Shipyards
but for the most part, it's accurate.
This is Grove 16.
Groves 1 to 29 are more or less a lawless zone.
That's why there are so many bounty-hunters around.
Couldn't you have said that sooner?!
If you had, you could have taken Sanji or Zoro instead of me!
It's fine now. Our destination, Grove 13, is next.
Chopper-chin, Skeleton-chin, you were both really strong and cool!
That doesn't make me happy at all, you jerk!~
I am quite embarrassed, so much that my entire face is red...
Though being a skeleton, I have no...
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove 13
Well then, we're here!
We finally made it here!
The store is on the top of that root.
Wonder if it's still open. It's been 10 years after all.
Say, is the coating mechanic a fishman, too?
Oh, Pappag and I haven't met him before.
We've heard that he's quite amazing, though.
Oh, really?
Shakki's Rip-off Bar
Shakki's Rip-off Bar?!
Hachi... This place seems like a total rip-off...
That mechanic isn't some sort of monster, is he?
It's fine! They're nice people.
I've known them since I was a kid.
Hey, it says "Bar"! Is that really okay?
Seems they're open.
Rayleigh, Shakki!
Bar Owner Former Pirate
Shakuyaku (Shakki)
Welcome.
What can I do for you?
Oh, my...
Could it be, Hacchan?
Long time, no see!
Sorry it's been so long, Shakki.
That's right. It's been at least ten years, hasn't it?
Just sit down and wait. I've gotta finish extorting the money out of these boys here.
Take your time.
I'll finish it quickly.
Is that so? You quit being a pirate, Hacchan?
Plenty of things happened...
Well, good for you. Honesty is the best way to go, after all.
By the way, it's not often that you see a mermaid above the sea...
Camie-chan, are you Hacchan's girlfriend?
N-N-No way, I... I couldn't become Hacchin's b-b-b-bride!
You're overreacting.
She works with me at the Takoyaki stand.
Oh, is that it?
That's right... Would you like something to drink...?
Shakki-san, these beans are quite tasty.
He's already raided the fridge?!
Luffy! Brook! She's gonna rip you off!
It's okay I don't mind.
Well, then, I'll give you something good.
Here.
Cotton candy?!
It's great!
Right. It'll cost you 100,000 belly.
I... I...
Don't have that much...
Sorry! It was a joke!
I won't ask for payment from Hacchan's friends.
Really?
Lady, how'd you know what Chopper's favourite food was?
You're Monkey-chan's crew, right?
You know me?
Of course. You're the crew everyone talks about.
I'm pretty well-informed.
Really? Luffy-chin, you're famous?
Though, I didn't know you had a skeleton in your crew,
or that a living skeleton existed, for that matter.
There, thank you for waiting.
Thanks!
I read an article about you guys.
About the Enies Lobby incident...
How much of it is true?
Is it true that you picked a fight with the government?
Whatever, it's too much trouble to tell you.
Not gonna brag?
What a big shot.
Come to think of it, your name is the same as that marine, Garp, right?
Yeah, he's my grandpa.
I thought so.
I used to be chased around by him all the time.
Why?
Shakki used to be a pirate.
Really?
I gave up about forty years ago, though.
But then... How old are you, granny?
These days, I think it's fun supporting rookies like yourselves.
By the way, Shakki...
No need to say it. I know, all of it.
The reason why you and Camie-chan came here,
was to help Monkey-chan and his crew get their ship coated, right?
That was good!
Here.
In other words, you've got a job for Rayleigh, right?
That's right.
But, he isn't here.
Huh? The mechanic isn't around?
We wanna go to Fishman Island!
Well, there's no way he'd leave this archipelago, so...
How about looking for him in the bars and gambling houses?
Then, we'll just wait until he comes back.
That's right. He'll be back eventually...
He's been gone for half a year, though.
Half a year?!
I'm sure he's found girlfriends, and thus found places to sleep,
so I am not exactly worried about his health.
I suppose it's just how ex-pirates are. Once they leave, they won't return for a long time.
The old mechanic guy was a pirate, too?!
But this is quite a problem...
If he isn't here, I suppose we have no choice but to look for him.
Do you have any idea where we should start?
Let's see...
He's probably somewhere between Grove 1 and 29...
He's quite notorious, so he can't lower his guard when there are marines around.
And then... if he's not there... he also likes going to the Sabaody Park.
The amusement park?!
Alright! We'll look there!
The amusement park!
Hey, Camie!
Amusement park! Amusement park!
Anyway, wherever you go to look for him, be careful.
According to my information, now that you've arrived, there should be...
Eleven people on the Sabaody Archipelago with bounties exceeding 100 million Berry.
11 people... exceeding 100 million Berry?!
Not counting Monkey-chan and Roronoa-chan, there are nine others.
When you entered the Grand Line,
there were seven paths you could take and you chose one of them,
and have been following the Log on that path ever since, right?
Yeah.
Of course, there were also people who chose one of the other six routes...
and made it through all sorts of trouble to get here, just like yourselves.
No matter what route you take, each of them eventually leads to the Red Line...
and to get past that wall, everyone comes to this archipelago.
Understand?
Though it's pretty amazing that all of the world's rookies
managed to show their faces here at the same time.
In particular, there's Kid, Luffy, Hawkins, Drake, and Law.
These names have been decorating the newspapers for some time now.
I don't read the news.
If we're going by bounty value,
you're number two among them.
There's someone on this island with a higher bounty than Luffy?!
Grove 24
-Restaurant-
What a crazy eating rate...
How can she fit all of it in that body?
Bring me more!
What a vulgar woman...
She's making me lose my apetite.
Silence her.
That's not a good idea, Father! This town is right next to the Navy HQ!
If we cause an uproar here...
West Blue Native
Leader of the Firetank Pirates
Capone "Gang" Bege.
Bounty
138 Million Belly
Bounty, 138 million belly.
Isn't the food here yet?!
Hurry and bring it here!
It seems they're cooking it as fast as they can, captain.
But, they won't make it in time, at this rate!
Get me more pizza!
South Blue Native
Captain of the Bonney Pirates
"The Glutton" Jewelry Bonney.
Bounty
140 million belly
Bounty, 140 million belly.
W-We'll bring you your food immediately.
P-Please forgive me!
Why, you...!
Stop it.
Why would I, captain?!
He got spaghetti on my clothes!
That was the fate of those clothes.
Please forgive us for startling you.
Today, is a bad day for new acquaintances.
North Blue Native
Captain of the Hawkins Pirates
"The Magician" Basil Hawkins.
Bounty
294 Million Belly
Bounty, 249 million belly.
What's that? A fight?!
If you wanna fight, why not wait until we've gotten past the wall?
Huh? Don't you know how strong we are?
Grand Line Native
Captain of the On-Air Pirates
"Roar of the Sea" Scratchmen Apoo.
Bounty
198 Million Belly
Bounty, 198 million belly.
Well then, stop staring at me.
Boss! Don't do it!
You're such a disgusting guy.
I don't mind finishing you off right now, you know?
South Blue Native
Captain of the Kid Pirates
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
Bounty
315 Million Belly
Bounty, 315 million belly.
The mad monk's gone berserk!
We've got to hurry and get away from here!
If you want to cause a stir...
then do it in the New World!
North Blue Native
Captain of the Drake Pirates
"Red Flag" X-Drake.
Bounty
222 Million Belly
Bounty, 222 million belly.
I see.
The former officer, Drake, huh?
Sky Island Native
Captain of the Depraved Monk Pirates
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
Bounty
180 Million Belly
Bounty, 108 million belly.
Your life was just spared, masked man.
South Blue Native
Warrior of the Kid Pirates
"Massacre Soldier" Killer.
Bounty
162 Million Belly
Bounty, 162 million belly.
It was just getting good...
Yo, Drake. How many people have you killed?
North Blue Native
Captain of the Heart Pirates
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law.
Bounty
200 Million Belly
Bounty, 200 million belly.
All of the pirate crews that entered the Grand Line,
have been reduced to an easily countable number.
The Grand Line is like a huge survival tournament.
Regardless of which path they traveled, the ones that survived this far are truly the elites.
Among them, there might be one,
who will become a huge leading figure for the next generation of pirates.
Regardless, even the New World won't remain un-fazed if so many big shot rookies enter at once.
Also, the reason why Captain Kid has a higher bounty than you...
is because his crew has badly injured civilians.
Not too cute, right?
Because of that, I'm whole-heartedly cheering for your crew, Monkey-chan.
Well, for now...
I think I'll just enjoy myself.
Oh, but if there are so many in town, I'm kinda worried...
about the old mechanic dude.
You don't have to worry about my people.
He's a hundred times stronger than you boys, after all.
A hundred...
times?
Well, be careful then.
I should tell you, of course, the Navy already knows...
that there are so many high-level rookies gathered on this archipelago.
That is bad...
Then, they could come at us at any time?
Oh, that shouldn't be a problem.
I wonder if this will speed up the meeting among rookies?
Right now, the Navy HQ is so busy with something else,
that they don't have the time to worry about you.
Or at least, I assume so.
As long as no huge problems pop up on the archipelago,
The Navy shouldn't send any major force here to deal with you.
So in short, just take care not to start any kind of uproar alright?
Oh, so that's how it is?
Gotcha! Thanks!
We're off to look for the old mechanic dude!
Yeah...that's a problem, huh?
But are you sure about this?
Yeah, Peterman-san...
Kidnapping Team "Hound Pets"
Boss Peterman
That woman who was with Straw Hat Luffy and the others was probably...
a mermaid!
When I remember what I saw...
Crap! Camie! Pappag!
The woman's shoe fell off at one point, and there wasn't a foot, but a fin!
Really now?
But it'll be a problem as long as she's with those strong guys, huh?
That being said, a mermaid on land gives us a huge chance!
After all, you can't catch'em underwater.
Thanks a lot for telling me, you guys!
As a reward, you can have 10% of the fee we fetch for her, all right?
Ah, if possible, could we have 20%?
Huh?!
No, 10% is enough! Thanks a lot!
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove 32, 33, 34
Amusement Park
"Sabaody Park"
We've reached Sabaody Park!
Yay!
Awesome! It looks so fun!
You're not even gonna LOOK for the old guy, are you?!
But the old lady said the old mechanic dude likes it here!
But that was only if he wasn't in the lawless zone!
The ferris wheel!
This is the first time I've been this close to it!
Right! Then, you guys, let's go have fun!
Yeah!
You're not gonna look, huh?!
Yay!
Camie! You can't go in there!
No way I'd let you go in!
We are rising quite slowly, aren't we?
What a nice view...
That's right. I truly prefer slow-moving attractions like this one...
Such a really nice view...
Hey, you guys rotated it too fast!
What did you think would happen when you did that anyway?!
You can't do that!
Wow!
We're so high up!
Awesome! Amazing!
I can see it all from here!
You're so happy that you're crying?
Yes, because...
this has been my dream since I was a child...
This is the first time I've been to a place as high as this!
I'll remember it for the rest of my life! Thank you!
Hacchin and Pappag let me come here because you guys are so strong!
It's like everything I dreamed of as a kid came flooding back!
All young fishmen and mermen dream of coming here!
Super-high!
Let's ride that next!
A gondola!
Yeah!
Captain Urouge... Is that...?
Oh, my...
Celestial Dragon St. Charlos
A Celestial Dragon, huh?
Casually taking a stroll in the lawless zone...
He's just asking for trouble.
Let's get on our knees and wait it out, guys.
Sharlia and Father have just left me behind...
Where did they get off to?
We know where they were going, so you need not worry.
Brat! You walk as slowly as a turtle!
Also, your ride is the worst!
This guy, he makes me sick!
Hey! You guys, wait!
Why are you moving? You're just humans and all...
We're sorry! Please, let this slide!
This man is bleeding terribly!
It seems like he's been caught up in a fight!
The hospital is right ahead, too...
It's true, this is quite an injury...
Then, I suppose I'd better hurry...
and put him to rest!
Please, stop!
Oh, my...
Just doing as he pleases, huh?
My well-deserved respect or the lives of lower-class citizens...
Which is moore important?!
It is only through your mercy that they are given life.
I've decided! I shall make you my wife!
What?!
Then, I shall start the paperwork to have her brought to the Holy Land as Lady 13.
Ooh, I am tired of wives 1 to 5, so you may return them to the lower classes.
I understand.
Please wait! I...
Please wait! She's my fiancé!
Another one dares too stand up before me?!
Mary...
No!
No, you murderer! How could you?!
Someone, please... Please help him!
He's just messed up...
Even more so than they said he was...
What?
Do you have any complaints about me?
Please let me go! I'm begging you!
Take her too the port!
Yes!
Who's that?
Captain Apoo! He's the Pirate Hunter from East Blue!
Why is he walking in the middle of the road?! Doesn't he know anything?!
He'll get us all in trouble, that guy!
Huh? You want me to give you directions or something?
Hey, hey! What's he planning to do?
A kid...?
Brother!
Why'd you die?
Brother, stay still.
Brother!
You tried to attack the Celestial Dragon-sama?!
Then of course you'd die!
I hit him?
For a moment, it seemed as though he had dodged it...
Was I imagining things?
Well, as long as he's dead, then it's fine.
Why'd you get in my way?
Huh? Don't say we got in your way, you dumbass!
What the hell were you trying to do?!
Do you WANT the admirals to come to this island?!
Tomato juice...
Even pirates have their own unspoken laws, you know!
You just caused us a whole lot of trouble too!
Trouble?
You're...
Huh? Wasn't there a kid here?
Are you even listening to me?! Are you right in the head?!
Uh, I'm not hurt or anything...
Idiot, I'm talking about what's inside!
You're such a moron!
Completely brain-dead!
Thanks to Jewelry Bonney, it seems we avoided the worst outcome...
That man is from the Straw Hat crew, Pirate Hunter Zoro.
I heard that crew has done nothing but anger the Government,
but I didn't think they'd be so stupid as to attack the Celestial Dragons.
Of course he was spared.
I do not see the mark of death upon him.
That bastard...
For a moment, he really was ready to kill him...
What a beast.
A second-in-command worth 120 million...
He doesn't seem like the type who'd follow orders...
I guess that's saying something about his captain, huh?
Hey, where's the hospital?
The hospital?
I'll bring this guy there. He got shot.
Just leave that stranger alone!
I don't believe it.
A pirate helping someone? Never heard of that before...
I just had a look around town.
People were flying around on these bubble-bikes!
Oh, I saw it, I saw it! Those were cool, weren't they?
Let's buy one!
We've gotta find out how they ride'em!
Oh, maybe that's from Nami-san?
Hi, Nami-swa-
Hello?!
It's me!
It's Chopper!
Um, there were so many different kinds of ice cream...
We weren't paying attention!
Hey, what are you so upset about?
Sanji?!
Something terrible just happened! What do we do?!
You're not making any sense! Calm down and tell me what happened!
What's up, Sanji?
Camie has been kidnapped!
What did you say?!
It's probably that team of slave-traders who did it!
I don't understand the reason,
but mermen and fishmen get sold off at the market, regardless of whether they've actually done anything!
They took Camie away!
If she ends up being a slave for the rest of her life, it'll be our fault!
There are so many human shops on the archipelago,
so we have no idea where they're taking her!
And we don't even know who took her!
The archipelago is too big, but if everyone lends a hand, then maybe...
Tell me where you guys are right now.
We'll meet up there.
Huh? But...!
We'll contact a guy who's a pro at this stuff.
I'll call the Flying Fish Riders!
Yahoo! It's me, Handsome!
No, that's wrong!
It's Duval!
Greetings, Master Black Leg!
You're late, Flying Fish Riders!
Wait a minute, young master...
We are the Rosy Life Riders!
I don't care what you call yourselves! You're annoying!
Anyway, a mermaid was kidnapped. That's why we contacted you.
Huh? So the slave-traders showed up, huh?
Those guys are unBerryevable!
Hey, weren't YOU slave-traders too?!
There are so many places they could have gone to, so...
You guys! Give us a hand!
Why, of course! Thank you for your orders!
Thank you very much!
Will we really be alright with these guys?
But first, the Handsome me just went to a city where I could find some women.
Huh?
As I expected, I...
couldn't get any...
I might have restructured your face, but I can't restructure your heart, you know.
But don't mind that! I got it, young masters!
We just have to find that mermaid before she's sold, right?
That's right. You guys should know a thing or two about the Sabaody Archipelago, right?
Of course!
We know the seas around here like our own backyard!
Just think of it as having gotten on a really big ship!
Now, get on!
So we are going on this flying fish?
Yes, friend!
I'm counting on you!
Gotcha!
So, how are we gonna look for them?
Young master, people in this business have their own way of doing things.
We already have information on the various slave-trader teams.
First of, we'll pick up the Straw Hats who are spread all over the Sabaody Archipelago!
And at the same time, we'll also track down the slave-traders who took that mermaid!
Let's get going, you guys!
Yeah!
Sabaody Park
Is this really okay?
Sanji, what do I do?
Listen, Chopper! No matter what, don't move!
We'll come get you no matter what!
Got it...
Hey, Luffy! Sanji said we should stay where we...
In times like this, it's dangerous for us to get separated, right...
Brook?
You're too relaxed! I was really shocked!
Camie was kidnapped, you know!
If she gets sold, she'll end up being a slave for the rest of her life!
Chopper-san,...
Sanji-san was very specific as to what we should do next.
No matter how we spend it, we will still be waiting for a certain amount of time.
I see.
Head, we've arrived at Sabaody Park!
Pick up each one of the Straw Hats, one by one!
Yeah!
The #5 public snail-phone should be somewhere around here.
Yeah, it's here! There they are! Those two on that bench!
Hey, you two!
What the...?!
Why are you so freaking relaxed?
Let's go! We're initiating our great plan to save Camie!
Yes! It's time to give it our best! Let's go!
We... we got yelled at, Brook!
Ashamed! I am slightly ashamed!
Split up and keep going! Investigate all of the slave-trading organizations.
Find out who did it! And don't forget to pick up the remaining Straw Hats!
Understood! We're splitting up!
Alright! Hurry up, Rosy-Life Riders!
There's not a minute to lose!
That should do it.
That's not enough! Can't you do anything about this cow?!
I should have gone on a flying fish too!
Huh? Did you just say that I'm handsome?
I never said that! You're the damn Head, aren't you, Duval?!
Why aren't you the fastest one in the team?!
What are you saying?
Of course I'm the most handsome one in the team!
Just speed this thing up, you moron!
Alright, we're here!
Meanwhile
Grove 22 Human Shop
Are you sure nobody tried to sell you a mermaid here?
I'm sure! Nobody has been here!
Stop it, Straw Hat! If you cause a commotion, it'll just make it harder to look!
Squid! Let's search the store!
Alright.
Hey!
How'd it go, squid, Pappag?
She's not here.
Camie!
Guess there's no helping it... Let's look somewhere else, Straw Hat.
Well, wait a minute. It seems that we have one mermaid here after all.
Really, there's a mermaid here?!
The only mermaid we have here is this lady here, Marin!
She's nice and cheap too. Want her?
Will you buy me, boy?
You're not a mermaid!
Wait, aren't you that guy we saw earlier?!
It's hard to breathe in water!
Hey!
Camie!
Where are you?!
We don't know if she's been sold yet...
If only we knew who took her, at least...
Hey, look at that!
That's Straw Hat Luffy from East Blue!
Damn it! This is my fault!
I knew that the amusement park is the best spot for the slave-traders...
and how much they'd want to capture a mermaid...!
Hey, these guys have so many types of ice-cream, huh? What do you guys want?
Hey, let me pick one too!
Camie, wait here for a minute.
Sure! Pick out a tasty one for me too.
I don't want that to be my last conversation with Camie!
It's my fault... It's because I let her go to the amusement park...!
Yes, because...
this has been my dream since I was a child...
This is the first time I've been to a place as high as this!
I'll remember it for the rest of my life! Thank you!
I'm not sure I understand, but she was so happy!
It was fine to bring her to the amusement park, wasn't it?!
No, it wasn't!
Actually, mermen and fishmen shouldn't even be on this island in the first place.
But...
...Hachi just wanted to help you guys out no matter what-
Pappag! Don't say any more!
What's he talking about? Why can't you guys be on this island?
Camie and Hachi's enemies here aren't just the slave-traders.
Every single human living on this archipelago is an enemy!
200 years ago?
Grove 30
Shopping Mall
Yes. Until just 200 years ago, that dark history was reality...
Fishmen and mermen were considered normal fish,
and were discriminated by humans all over the world.
Everyone looked down upon them.
Those strong fishmen?
Even the strongest creatures are powerless when outnumbered.
This continued until the World Government decided to lend a helping hand to Fishman Island 200 years ago.
That's just another piece of the dark history of the human race.
On this archipelago, slave-trading and selling of human lives is still acceptable.
So I think, maybe the discrimination of mermen and fishmen is still common here, too.
Discrimination?
I'm the fool here for not remembering that this is one island to avoid...
That's why I should have stopped Camie, no matter how cruel I'd have to be...
Then, could that be the reason why Hachi and Camie had to disguise themselves on this island?
I hope I'm just reading too much into things, though.
Bratty girl! Robin!
Franky!
Hey, stop calling me "bratty girl"!
Hurry up and get on the flying fish! That mermaid was kidnapped!
Camie-chan?!
Kidnapped?!
Camie...!
Sorry, Straw Hat... I just wanted to help, but I ended up causing you trouble...
What're you guys saying?
I never thought you did anything wrong!
The three of you are my friends!
No matter what might happen, we'll definitely save Camie!
So stop crying!
Straw...
You...!
Straw Hat!
It's the Flying Fish Riders!
We've been looking for ya... Get on!
Hey, squid... Are you gonna fly too?
Yeah!
Sabaody Archipelago - Grove 1
Human Auction House
Back Door
Be sure to get a good price for her!
She'll definitely catch a high price! Come back for your share later!
I'll look forward to it!
Oh, my! Saint Roswald! Lady Sharlia! Welcome!
I'm afraid that it will be hard for everyone to get on their knees while talking inside the hall...
I do not mind. They may bid freely.
Thank you very much! Well then, let me take you to the VIP seats.
Big Brother Charlos is so late...
It is because he chose to ride on a lowly human.
If he was going to ride, he should have used a fishman.
They have 10 times the strength of a man, after all.
Celestial Dragons... Slaves... The Human Shop...
That's...
Captain Kid, from South Blue!
Compared to the "righteous" greed of the rulers,
the villains of the world seem much more honorable.
When scum rules the world, only more scum is born...
You don't even understand that?
At least we're honest about being bad people, right Killer?
You're right.
How about we buy anyone who seems interesting?
Chief Kid, look at that.
I know that face...
It's the 200-million man from North Blue, Trafalgar Law.
I heard some bad rumors about him.
His manners are bad, too.
Auction Host
Waiting Room
Disco-san!
We've got something incredible today!
Today's big draw is a giant, right? I already know.
Leave it to me. I'll be sure to get a good price for him.
Are the cherry blossoms prepared yet?
Wrong! It's a mermaid! A young mermaid!
I'm sure the bidding war will be fierce!
Really?
Let me go! That hurts!
No, Hacchin!
Why, this one...! If you don't want to get hurt, then stay still!
Hey, don't be so rough with such an important item!
Disco-san!
Oh, so this is the one? The mermaid that just came in...
Yes.
How rare! She seems lively and healthy!
We should fetch quite the price for this one!
Who brought her here?
The Hound Pets.
Peterman, huh? He's done a great job.
Doesn't seem like the Flying Fish Riders brought in anything this time, though.
Well, regardless, this one should bring in a lot of money.
What's with that face?!
Why you...!
You're just a damn fish! Know your place!
Wait, Disco-san! She's an important item! If you hurt her, her value will drop!
If you have to kick her then at least, do it somewhere where her clothes will cover it, like her stomach!
Hacchin will definitely come and beat you up!
She still has the nerve to talk back to me...
Hey! Give me the neck ring!
Yes...
I'll put this on her.
No!
Disco-san!
Hey, what happened, Disco-san?!
The show is just about to start, too!
Doctor! Get a doctor!
Hey, gramps!
Quit pretending.
That was you, right? That "Haki" just now.
Who the hell are you?
Just an old man who coats ships.
Former first mate of the
Roger Pirates
I simply
love
"The right hand of the Pirate King"
Silvers Rayleigh
young girls.